《越狱》前情提要
Previously on Prison Break:
要去哪里，老弟？
So where to, man?
想去哪儿都行
Anywhere we want.
我已不是你 记忆中的哥哥，我变了
I'm not the brother you remember. I've changed.
我要去做一件事
And I am gonna do something...
很多人将会 认为我罪不可赦
...a lot of people are gonna think is horrible.
我只要你记住 和你一同长大的哥哥
And you just remember the brother you grew up with,
她还没到
she's not here.
-喂？ -莎拉，船要开了
- Yeah? - Sara, the ship is leaving.
我已经上船了
I'm already onboard.
我爱你
Love you,
你现在说这些做什么？
Why are you telling me this now?
如果能重新来过
If I had to do it all over again...
我一定会做出不同的决定
...I'd do it different, you know.
伤口在锁骨和旋转肌之间
Collarbone and rotator cuff.
再往右移六寸你就死了
Six inches to the right and you're dead.
你已经辛苦的走到这地步了
- You've come so far. - How much further would I have to go?
-我还要再走多久？ -算你幸运
-这次你只要去巴拿马 -非常感谢你
You're lucky. For this, you only have to go to Panama.
-他找到他了 -在哪里？
- He found him. - Where?
-他刚搭飞机去巴拿马市 -他去巴拿马干嘛？
- Just boarded a plane to Panama City. - What's he doing in Panama?
-你喜欢假发吗？ -只要钱够多，我什么都喜欢
- You like wigs? - For the right money, I like anything.
留言板有消息吗？ 那个金翅网站？
What about the message board? The Goldfinch thing?
-有一则苏克的留言 -他还在逃亡？
- There is a message from sucre. - Still running, huh?
他说钱还在茶包手上
He says, "The Bag still has the bag.
他在巴拿马市的终点旅馆
He's in Panama City at the Fin Del Camino Hotel.
如果你在那儿 想帮忙抓他
If you're there and wanna help put that bird in the cage...
-通知我一声，苏克留 -到时见
...let me know. Sucre." - See you soon.
（克莉丝汀娜玫瑰号 巴拿马）
Christina Rose PANAMA
迈克！
Michael!
（巴拿马，巴拿马市）
（奥立维拉大道三一二号 二楼，红色门）
斯科菲尔德，你真和大家 说的一样唇红齿白
Scofield, one thing's for sure, You're just as pretty as advertised,
-其实还更俊俏 -请你救救我，拜托
- Prettier even, - You've gotta help me. Please.
我要来抓你了 准备好了吗？
I'm coming for you, Are you ready?
不！
No.
我要来找你了
I'm coming for you,,,,
敢出声我就割开 你的喉咙，老婊子
say a word and I will cut your throat out, you old whore.
斯科菲尔德
Scofield.
-喂 -潘，是我
- Hello, - Pam, it's me.
（计程车6T-13807 巴拿马）
- Cam's napping, - Yeah? How's he doing?
-小卡在睡午觉 -是吗？他还好吗？
很好，今天 他回学校上课了
Good, It was his first day back in school,
-太好了 -你在哪里？
- That's great. - Where are you?
我在国外
I'm out of the country.
没事吧？
Is everything all right?
记得我常说 总有一天我会辞职吗？
Remember how I always said that the day would come and I'd be done?
-头也不回地离开调查局？ -记得
- Leave the Bureau and never look back? - Yes,
那天就是今天
Today's that day.
我还有一件事要做
I have one more thing to do.
只要等我做完
And once I do it...
一切都会恢复原状 我就不干了
...everything is gonna fall into place and I'll be done.
-希望你是真心的 -潘
- Well, I hope you mean it, - Pam.
如果我不再做这工作 如果我自由了
If I didn't have this job anymore, or if I were free...
如果我自由了
If I were free...
-亚历 -我需要知道你的想法
- Alex, - I need to know.
我没有打算拒绝你
I'm not saying no,
我会好好补偿你们 我发誓
I will make this right, I swear to God.
然后你、我和小卡
And you and me and Cam...
我得挂电话了
I have to go,
我对你的爱 从来没停止过，潘
I've never stopped loving you, Pam.
-从来没有 -小心一点，亚历
- Ever. - Just be safe, Alex,
-你们就位了吗？ -是的
- You in position? - Yeah,
-我十分钟后到 -了解
- I'll be there in 10 minutes, - Got it.
迈克
Michael.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
你好吗，斯科菲尔德？
Que pasa, scofield?
快点走了
Come on, move it.
真有趣
I love it.
连高尚先生 也来这里找那五百万
Mr. Above-It-All down here trying to sniff out that 5 million...
跟我们这些粗人一样
...just like the rest of us riff-raff.
瞧，你也不见得比我好
See, you ain't no better than me.
我要把茶包抓起来 这是我来这里唯一的原因
I want T-Bag locked up. That's the only reason I'm here.
当起正义骑警了是吗？
Oh, Dudley freaking Do-Right, huh?
-我不知道你会来这里 -你在胡说什么？
- I didn't know you were here. - What are you talking about?
你传讯给我说茶包在这里 你在网站上留言
You e-mailed me, said T-Bag was here. It's on the website.
什么？没有 我没在网站上留言
What? No. I didn't write anything on no website.
我没留言给任何人
To you or anybody else.
茶包在那家旅馆里吗？
Is T-Bag in that hotel?
对，对街还有 两个联邦探员在监视
Yeah, and a couple of feds staking it out across the street.
-你要帮我们拿到钱 -你没听到我讲联邦探员吧
- You're gonna help us get it. - Maybe you missed the part about the feds.
我不管，我跋涉两千里 一路上狂拉肚子
I don't care. I didn't travel 2000 miles down the Diarrhea Trail...
来到这落后的烂国家 就是要我的五百万！
...to get to this backward-ass country to not get my 5 million.
真可惜 这情况越看越像陷阱
Well, that's too bad. This is looking more and more like a setup.
那就把你聪明的小脑袋 拿出来用
Well, then, get that little college boy brain of yours to work, then.
如果你不相信我，问问你的狱友 我能做到什么地步
And if you don't think I'm serious, just ask your old cellie here what length I'll go to.
他把犸丽关在某个地方
He's got Maricruz locked away somewhere.
我一定得帮他 不然她就死定了
Either I help him get the money, or she's dead.
对，我是大浑蛋 斯科菲尔德，我真无耻
Yeah, I'm a big jerk, scofield. Shame on me.
迈克，我没有资格 求你帮助我
Michael, I'm in no position to ask you for anything.
但我需要你帮忙，老哥
I need your help, papi,
是真的
I do.
你到底要不要加入？
Are you in, or what?
片名：越狱风云
剧名：穷途末路
-把枪拿开 -我刚刚问你问题
- Get the gun off me. - I asked you a question.
我说把枪拿开 不然我就走人
I said get the gun off me, or I walk.
好，你会拿到五百万
All right, you'll get your 5 million...
你救回犸丽 我抓到茶包
...you get Maricruz and I get T-Bag.
-好一个三赢局面 -但你们要完全照我的话去做
- Win-win-win. - But you gotta do exactly what I say.
谢谢你，老哥
Thank you, bro.
好，小天才
All right, Einstein.
有何打算？
What you thinking?
今天是莎拉丹奎迪医生一案 开庭第三天
And it's the third day of testimony in the trial of Dr, Sara Tancredi,,,
她是已故的 弗兰克丹奎迪州长之女
,,, daughter of the late Governor Frank Tancredi,
目前各方认为 检方需做的举证
So far, pundits feel the prosecution is well on its way,,,
将非常顺利 能将所有罪名定罪
,,, to meeting its burden of proof and getting a conviction on all counts,
被告律师，请
Defense counsel, you may proceed.
庭上，我要求将录影带 列为辩方证物D
Your Honor, at this time, I ask that this tape be marked Defense Exhibit D.
抗议，庭上 这卷录影带只不过是
Objection. Your Honor, this tape is the very propaganda...
迈克斯科菲尔德和林克柏劳 给媒体的宣传手段
...that Michael scofield and Lincoln Burrows released to the media...
而且还立刻被揭穿
...that was summarily debunked.
-陪审团还是有权利看 -这影带是道听途说
- The jury still has a right to hear it. - The tape is hearsay.
证人无法到场
Unavailable Witness Exception.
证人无法到场是因为 他是在逃亡的通缉犯
The witness is only unavailable because he's a fugitive on the run.
就算如此，他在影带里的自白 证明丹奎迪医生是清白的
Be that as it may, his statement on this tape exonerates Dr. Tancredi.
庭上
Your Honor...
我允许播放录影带
The tape is allowed.
纪录上会注明检方反对
The state's objection will be noted in the record.
另一位无辜的人也遭到责难 莎拉丹奎迪医生
Much blame has been placed on another innocent person, Dr, Sara Tancredi,
她与我们越狱毫无关联
She had nothing to do with our escape,
莎拉，你在听的话 我知道无法求你再给我机会
Sara, if you're listening, I know I can't ask you for another chance,
我只希望现在 你已找到你的安全港
I only hope by now, you've found your safe haven,
已故丹奎迪州长之女 莎拉丹奎迪医生的案子
The trial of the late Governor Tancredi's daughter, Dr, Sara Tancredi,,,
目前还在库克郡进行
,,, continues today in cook county,
丹奎迪医生的 执业执照已遭暂停
Dr, Tancredi, whose medical license has been suspended,,,
（丹奎迪受审）
,,, pending the outcome of the trial, is facing multiple counts, ranging...
等待审判的结果 她正面临多项指控，包括
-我要杀了他 -你会被关回牢里
- I'm gonna kill him. - And go back to prison.
我不在乎
I don't care.
等拿到钱，他说出犸丽的 下落后，我就要杀了他
Once we get the money and he tells me where Maricruz is I'm gonna kill him.
等你找到犸丽 你要娶她为妻，过幸福的日子
If you find Maricruz, you're gonna marry Maricruz and live happily ever after.
对，但我要先给 贝里克一刀
Yeah, after I sink a knife in Bellick's chest.
贝里克和茶包会得到报应 相信我
Bellick and T-Bag will get theirs, trust me.
你在福克斯河没学到吗？
Didn't Fox River teach you anything?
外面的世界跟里面 没什么两样
Because the same rules apply out here.
不管你是不是有罪都一样
It doesn't make a difference if you're guilty or innocent.
-生存最重要 -你不是那种人
- It's who survives. - You're not that guy.
那浑蛋把我的女友 抓去关起来
That son of a bitch took my girl and locked her up.
我现在是那种人，迈克
I am that guy now, Michael.
你看看我
Look at me.
我现在还留在此地 唯一的理由
Only reason I'm not five miles away from here...
是我想帮你找犸丽 而不是杀贝里克
...is because I wanna help you find Maricruz, not kill Bellick.
如果你有这种打算 我就走人
And if that's your game, I'm gone.
相信我，我能体会 想扣下板机的冲动
Believe me, I understand the impulse to pull the trigger.
但如果失去自我 我们就没救了
But if we lose ourselves, we lose everything.
都过一星期了
It's been a week.
-我不知道她在哪儿，我好害怕 -我们会找到她的
- I don't know where she is. I'm scared. - We'll find her.
我们会找到她的
We'll find her.
（火警铃 按下后往下拉）
怎么回事？
What the hell is this?
注意，各位先生女士
Attention, ladies and gentlemen, The fire alarm has been activated,
火灾警铃已启动 请依照人员指示离开
Please proceed to the nearest exit in an orderly manner,
你胡乱逞英雄 这件事很快就会没戏唱
You start acting like a cowboy, this whole thing's going south real fast.
记住这句话
Remember that.
开始了
Here we go.
待会儿的结局 你不会喜欢的，林克
You're not gonna like how this ends, Lincoln.
我现在给你一次机会
I'm giving you a chance right now.
退后，好吗？
Just back away, all right?
-退后 -你这浑蛋杀死我爸
- Just back away. - The son of a bitch who killed my dad?
你死定了
You're done.
你的枪伤 还没痊愈对吧，曼宏？
Those bullet holes don't heal too good, do they, Mahone?
把手铐丢给我
Toss me the handcuffs.
拿过来，不然我发誓 我会轰掉你的脑袋
Hand them over, or I swear to God, I'll blow your head clean off.
（三一二号）
你们是美国人吗？
Americans?
感谢老天，你们知道 瓜达鲁普大教堂在哪里吗？
Oh, thank God. You know where the Cathedral of Guadalupe is?
没听过这地方
Never heard of it.
我跟老婆半小时前 约在那里
Supposed to meet my old lady half hour ago.
-很好 -听说不可能错过，但我没看到
- That's great. - They say you can't miss it, but I missed it.
你们有没有 旅游导览之类的东西？
I was wondering if you had a travel guide or something on you?
请你走开好吗，老兄？
Why don't you just keep on walking?
还真是抱歉，我还以为 美国同胞会互相帮忙
Well, excuse me for thinking I could ask for a little help from some fellow Americans.
快滚
Hey, listen, beat it.
你们好吗，两位？
How we doing, gentlemen?
苏克，枪还我
All right, sucre, the gun.
快点
Come on.
到巷子里
Get in the alley.
（克莉丝汀凯勒曼）
这是个全球性的问题
It is a global problem.
北美有百分之四十八的湖泊 已经优养化
Forty-eight percent of North American lakes are eutrophic.
-欧洲有百分之五十三 -克莉丝汀
- It's 53 percent in Europe... - Kristine.
-什么事？ -是你哥哥保罗
- Yeah? - It's your brother, Paul.
怎么回事？
What? What's going on?
喂
Hello.
他就在这栋大楼里 我们动作得快
He's in this building right here. We gotta move.
证件交出来
Let's see your ID.
联邦探员？
Feds?
不是，如果是就会抓茶包 你们是“公司”的人？
No. If these guys were, they'd be after T-Bag. You guys Company?
苏克，快点 把这些浑蛋绑起来
Come on, sucre. Let's wrap these numbnuts up.
你们在这儿干嘛？ 有何目的？
What are you guys doing here? What do you want?
事情不妙，感觉有异
I don't like this. Something's up.
苏克，动作快
Come on, sucre, let's move it.
走吧，快点
Now. Let's go, come on.
走吧，迈克
Let's go, Michael.
我们知道你在这儿 包威！
We know you're in here, Bagwell.
三对一
Three to one.
你自己想想
Do the math.
好，好！我不想惹麻烦
Okay, okay. I don't want any trouble.
把枪放在地上滑过来
Slide the gun over.
我们可以谈条件，各位
We can work something out, boys.
把枪滑过来
Slide the gun over.
钱在哪里？
Where's the money?
谁报警的？
Who called the cops?
给你三秒钟，乡巴佬 一
You got three seconds, hillbilly. One...
在里面
In there.
去拿
Get it.
要就自己去拿
You want it, you get it.
没时间胡闹了，贝里克
We don't have time for this, Bellick.
别做傻事
Nothing stupid now.
不准你再玩把戏
You're not playing games.
开门
Open it.
苏克，过去开门！
Sucre, move your ass.
迈克
Michael.
这是陷阱
It's a trap.
站住，包威！
Freeze, Bagwell.
去拿钱
Get the money.
要救女友就去拿钱
You want the girl, get the money.
不要动
Don't.
别动
我们来谈条件吧
We can work something out.
过去
Move.
苏克，快来
Sucre, come on.
西奥多包威 才是杀死那马子的凶手
Theodore Bagwell. He's the one you want for that dead chick in there.
有人会说英文吗？不是我干的 我发誓不是我干的
Anybody speak English? I didn't do it. I swear to God I didn't do it.
拜托
Please, please.
我们可以在这里分钱 然后分道扬镖
We can do a little divvying right here. Then we'll go our separate ways.
苏克，帮忙准备一辆车
Sucre, I want you to get us a car.
怎么？要做什么？
What's going on? What's the plan?
我说去找辆车
I said get us a car.
看来你最近交了新朋友
Looks like you made some friends lately.
-我听不懂 -刚刚那场骗局
- I don't follow. - That little setup back there.
有点超出你的能力范围
It's a little out of your league.
几乎是专家的手法
Looked almost professional.
假设是如此 你有多想知道真相？
Let's say that's the case. What's it worth to you to find out, huh?
因为我是知道一些资讯
Because I am in possession of some information...
你可能会需要，帅哥
...that you might need, pretty.
好，知道的告诉我 我也许会让你走
Okay, tell me what you know. Maybe I'll let you walk.
但钱别想带走
Without the money.
-是吗？ -对
- Yeah? - Yeah.
-就这样让我大摇大摆地离开？ -要看你给我什么样的资讯
- You're gonna let me traipse on out of here. - Depends on the information.
是谁在幕后操控？
Who's pulling your strings?
我有预感你话中有话，帅哥
You know, I got a hunch you're speaking with a forked tongue, pretty.
不如这样，我们去公开场所
So I'm gonna tell you what. We go someplace public...
准备一辆车让我离开
...with a car waiting for me to leave and then...
到时我再告诉你 成交吗？
Then I'll tell you. Deal?
不成交
No.
天啊
Oh, my God.
保罗
Paul.
这是我这辈子第二次
That is only the second time...
遇到枪械卡弹的情况
...a weapon has ever jammed on me.
第一次是在 第一次波斯湾战争训练时
First time was during training for Gulf one.
一卡弹 指挥官就走到我面前说
And as soon as it happened, the C.o., he got in my face, and he said:
孩子，武器要是 在战场上卡弹
"Son, a weapon jam on the battlefield.
还不如直接去自杀
You might as well call that suicide."
克莉丝汀，我
Kristine, I've...
做了一些事
...done things...
-该死 -我爱你，保罗
- Damn. - I love you, Paul.
不管你为何走到这一步
Whatever it is that got you here.
一定有出路的，相信我
And there's a way out, believe me.
我成年后整个人生
My entire adult life...
都在听从命令
...I've followed orders.
我做了一些恐怖的事
And I did terrible things...
因为我以为这么做是对的
...because I thought they were right.
结果特勤局期间我做的事 全都毫无意义
And it turns out I did those things in the service of nothing.
所以我现在就是这样 一无所有
So that's what I'm left with. Nothing.
你还有我啊
You have me.
好
Okay.
而你还有未来
And you have a clean slate.
可塑性很高的未来
Anything, everything.
-现在就可以重新来过 -我做了好多坏事，克莉丝汀
- It's available to you starting right now. - The things I've done, Kristine.
你可以悔改
Undo them.
保罗，总是会有出路的
Paul, there's always a way.
也许那把枪卡弹 是有原因的
Maybe that gun jammed for a reason.
过来
Come here.
别让自尊误了大局，帅哥
Don't let your pride get in the way now, pretty.
省省吧
Save it.
把我关起来对你毫无帮助
Locking me up ain't gonna help your situation none.
我有你要的资讯
I have information.
-该怎么做？ -带他去大使馆
- What's the plan? - We're gonna take him to the embassy.
确定他会被遣返出境 我们再去找贝里克，好吗？
We're gonna make sure he's deported. Then we'll go looking for Bellick, all right?
还有，我要你 和他一起坐后座
Meanwhile, I want you to ride in the back with him.
我说真的 你会因小失大
I'm telling you, you are being penny wise and pound foolish.
上车
Get in the car.
失大局
Pound foolish, pound foolish, pound foolish.
我会告诉她 你们的条件
I'll tell her about the offer.
-如何？ -十二年
- Well? - Twelve years.
不陪审团 听到迈克的自白了
No, no, the jury heard Michael's statement.
他们只听到一个逃犯 为了深爱的女人说谎
They heard a convicted felon lie for a woman that he clearly cares for.
他的话不足采信
He's got no credibility.
莎拉，我们必须认真考虑 检方开的条件
Sara, we need to take a hard look at what they're offering.
恕我直言，马提 坐牢的不是我们，是我
Due respect, Marty, we aren't going to prison, I am.
他们摆明了 要有人背负责任
They've made it clear that they want somebody to hang for this...
不幸地是 现在他们手上只逮到你一人
...and unfortunately, you're the only one they've got in their grasp.
躲不了的
There's no avoiding it.
这是认罪同意书 我们可以仔细解说给你听
This is the plea agreement. We can walk you through it if you'd like.
十二年？
Twelve years?
他没有回应
He ain't answering.
我很希望你弟弟 能回到船上
I certainly hope your brother makes it back to that boat.
如果他没回去呢？
And if he doesn't?
你该看看你自己
You should see yourself.
你活像在崩溃边缘一样
You look like you're hanging in there by a thread.
我只想尽快结束这一切
I just want this over with.
那你就不该来这里
Then you should never have come down here.
你应该知道，我和我弟 不会为了任何人放弃
In case you hadn't noticed, me and my brother don't quit for no one.
感谢老天你们不会
Thank God for that.
因为有你们这种人 我们这些人才会有工作
Because it's guys accused of things like you were that keep guys like me in business.
应该说 曾经让我有工作
Kept guys like me in business, rather.
你不会有好下场的
It's gonna end bad for you, man.
世界上有些事我很拿手
A couple of things in this world I'm good at.
其中一项是我懂得 疲疚丧气的眼神是什么模样
One of them is looking into a man's eye and knowing when he's beat.
-大使馆还有多远？ -别急，兄弟
- How far to the embassy? - Just hang in there, buddy.
-到了之后呢？ -我们将他移送法办
- And then what? - We're gonna turn him in.
-我们要怎样不被逮到？ -到达之前，我会先停车
- And how do we not get busted? - Before we get there, I'll pull over.
我们用胶带把他绑起来 把他丢下车后离开
We'll hogtie him with duct tape, then we'll dump him out and hit the road...
我再报警 通知警方他在那里
...and I'll call the cops, tell them where we left him.
-要怎么找贝里克？ -别担心，会找到的
- How do we get to Bellick? - Don't worry, we'll find him.
-你们才不可能接近贝里克 -不关你的事
- Y'all ain't getting within a mile of Bellick. - Nobody asked you.
他说的有理，迈克
He's got a point though, Michael.
继续用枪指着他，可以吗？
Just keep the gun on him, okay?
如果贝里克被关起来 钱对他就没帮助了
I mean, if Bellick's locked up, what good's the money gonna be to him?
-我说会想办法的 -我的女友有生命危险
- We'll fix it. - My girl's life's on the line here.
-苏克，你最好振作 -天啊
- Sucre, you better pull it together... - oh, God.
救护车！救护车！
犸丽
Maricruz.
放轻松
Easy, easy.
-犸丽 -你不会有事的
- Maricruz, Maricruz. - You're gonna be all right.
把钱追回来，拜托
Go get the money, please.
过来！过来！
压住伤口
Pressure. Pressure.
你到底想要什么，帅哥？
What exactly is it that you want, pretty?
我要将你绳之以法
I'm turning you in.
真的就这样吗？
Is that it, really?
不是为了钱？ 如果是，你可以老实说
It ain't about the money? Because if it is, you can tell me.
这里只有我们两个罪犯
Ain't nobody here but us cons.
你可以乖乖就范 或是被我拖着离开
You can walk or get dragged...
自己决定
...but it's up to you.
不，知道吗？当你拿枪指着我 我多少还尊敬你
No, see, when you had the gun on me, I afforded you a certain respect.
但现在，掌控权在我手上
But here, well, the scales are tipped back my way.
所以该由我来说出 现在的选择
So I'm gonna spell out the present options.
我们可以把钱分掉
Either we split this money...
你就可以在腿上刺青 或是随便你想干嘛
...and you can go get your legs tattooed, or whatever the hell it is that you want.
不然你的尸体 会被发现架在那把椅子上
Or they're gonna find your corpse over that chair...
裤子还被我脱下 因为我觊觎你很久了
...with your pants down around your ankles because it's been a long time coming.
好，你回答我了
Well, I got my answer.
等你废话说完就来吧
Whenever you're done yakking.
放马过来，贱人
Bring it, bitch.
你在骗谁啊？
Who are you fooling?
你不会杀我的，白面书生
You ain't gonna kill me, Mr. Michelangelo.
你没这胆量 不如我们就
You ain't got it in you. So why don't we just let me...
好
All right.
好，莎拉
Okay, sara.
认罪的过程是这样的
Now, here's how the plea is going to go down.
法官会要你确认你的罪行
The judge is gonna need you to allocute to the charges.
他会问 你是否刻意不把门锁上
He's gonna ask you if you intentionally left the door open.
-你回答“是” -好
- You will say yes. - Right.
然后他会问你
And then he's gonna ask you:
你在迈克斯科菲尔德 和林克柏劳越狱之后
"Did you give support and comfort to Michael scofield and Lincoln Burrows...
是否有协助他们？“ 你回答”有
...since the escape?" You'll say yes.
接着法官会立刻判刑
And then the sentence will be immediately handed down.
检方要求让你去
The prosecution is asking that you do your time...
保安最严密的监狱服刑
...in a maximum security facility.
我认为法官会同意
I think the judge is going to agree to that.
好
Okay.
如果表现良好
With good behavior...
我要服刑多少年？
...how many years of my sentence can I expect to serve?
被判十二年
On a 12-year sentence...
你得坐九年牢
...you'll do nine years.
四十岁之前可以出狱
I'll be out before I'm 40.
很抱歉，莎拉
I'm sorry, sara.
莎拉，有新消息
Sara, are you ready for this?
什么事？
What?
有一个可信度很高的证人刚出面
A very credible witness has just come forward...
而且他愿意作证
...and he's willing to testify.
你所说的阴谋 他全部都可以证实
He'll corroborate everything you've said about this conspiracy.
是谁？
Who?
所有的小组注意
重复，受害者看到
加害人往东北方逃逸 进入丛林里
大约在三号公路 第三十六里处
（克莉丝汀娜玫瑰号）
林克？
Linc?
-你好，请问你会说英文吗？ -是，先生，我会
- Do you speak English? - Si, senor. Yes, I do,
好，我想要联络 巴拿马市所有的医院
Good, good. I need to get in contact with every hospital in the Panama City area.
我有个朋友
A friend of mine was...
我有个朋友出车祸了
A friend of mine was in a car accident.
先生？
Sir?
抱歉，我待会儿再打回去
I'm sorry, I'm gonna have to call you back.
林克？
Linc?
-对不起，迈克 -怎么回事？
- I'm sorry, Michael. - What's wrong?
你好，迈克
Hello, Michael.
如果你敢碰我哥 你就死定了
If you touch my brother, you're a dead man.
拜托
Oh, please,
你不用担心这种事
You don't have to worry about that.
不过到紧要关头时
But when it comes right down to it...
他跟你没有两样
,,, he's just like you,
他狠不下心杀人
He has a heart that won't kill a man.
把手铐给我，不然我发誓 我会轰掉你的脑袋
Give me the handcuffs, or I swear to God, I'll blow your head clean off.
你想怎样，亚历？
What do you want, Alex?
我会告诉你我想怎样 不过正事先办
I'll tell you exactly what I want. But first things first.
警方今天抓到 包威的时候
When the authorities captured Bagwell today...
那笔钱下落不明
...the money was nowhere to be found.
我只能猜想
Now, I can only assume...
钱在你手上
...that you've got the money...
现在就在 克莉丝汀娜玫瑰号上
,,, aboard the Christina Rose right now,
绝妙的计划 拿了钱搭船，然后永远消失
It's an amazing plan. Take the money, take the boat and disappear forever.
可是不光只有你需要消失
But you are not the only one that needs to disappear.
-你还在吗？ -我还在
- Are you still there? - Yeah, I'm still here.
很好，因为这句话 我只说一遍
Good, Because I'm gonna say this and I'm gonna say this once:
把钱和船都交给我
Bring me the money, bring me the boat.
你疯了
You are out of your mind.
没有
Not really.
我们手上都有 对方需要的东西
We both have something the other person needs.
迈克，重点就是
It all comes down to this, Michael:
用你的计划换你哥的命
Your brother for your plan,
我只给你五分钟考虑
Five minutes. That's what you have.